Guide to the Small Manuscript Collections
The Wittliff Collections
- Kiki Wheelock collection of Jeanne Dixon, 2009-2011
  - Clippings, photocopied photograph, letters, and awards related to Jeanne Dixon, co-author of The settlement of Leon Springs, Texas: from Prussia to Persia. Also includes book cover from this book, 2009-2011 (Folder SMC 0137)
- Kiki Wheelock collection of The Voyage of Islita, 2011; Wheelock, Kiki
  - Letters, promotional material, review and author biography relating to The Voyage of Islita by Kiki Wheelock, 2011 (Folder SMC 0138)